highlandwoodworking.com 2011-12-21

# Highland Woodworking's Privacy Statement

| 

##### Woodworking Tool Tips!

 tips on searching...

search for articles and information... 

|   
---  

---  
| | |   
---|---|---  
| 

Your Privacy

We appreciate the trust you place in Highland Woodworking and we are committed to respecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. Across our business, we recognize the importance of protecting all information provided us by customers, and we have procedures to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe and secure manner.

Highland Woodworking strictly adheres to the government's CAN-SPAM act and follows its guidelines in all aspects of our email marketing. We never share customer email addresses with third parties. We only send emails to customers who have offered their addresses to us to receive occasional information regarding woodworking tips, seminar information, industry developments and company promotions.

Our website is a secure site as authenticated through **VeriSign's Secure Site Pro with EV** , which uses 128-bit Extended Validation SSL, the strongest Secure Socket Layering encryption technology available to ensure safe Internet transmission of your personal information. Secure Socket Layering (SSL), the industry-standard encryption technology that ensures safe Internet transmission of your personal information. When the letters "http" in the URL change to "https," the "s" indicates you are in a secure area employing SSL; also, your browser may give you a pop-up message that you're about to enter a secure area. To further ensure the integrity of our security measures, HighlandWoodworking.com is continually monitored by McAfee Scan technology.

All personal information stored on our site is protected through digital certificates technology which functions as electronic credentials that allow secure communications between two parties. Digital certificates help identify user privileges as well as encrypt electronic messages over the Internet providing for safe data storage, online trading and credit card transactions.

Policy Statement

This is the web site of  
**Highland Hardware, Inc., d/b/a Highland Woodworking**  
Our postal address is  
**1045 North Highland Avenue  
Atlanta, GA 30306**

We can be reached via e-mail at [customerservice@highlandwoodworking.com](mailto:customerservice@highlandwoodworking.com)  
or you can reach us by telephone at 800-241-6748

  * For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). 
  * We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. 
  * With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart. 
  * If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address. 
  * We never share or rent customer email addresses. 
  * If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above. 
  * You may receive mailings from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by calling us at the number provided above. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations. 
  * Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. 
  * With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. 
  * From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. 
  * Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address. 
  * With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site. 
  * If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number. 

|   
| |   

|   
---  
    
[ ](http://www.highlandwoodworking.com/woodworking-tool-sale.html "Woodworking Tool Sale") **OUR NEW  
WINTER woodworking tool catalog is now available to browse online! _CLICK THE IMAGE  
TO BEGIN_** |  [](http://www.highlandwoodworking.com/woodworking-tool-catalog-1111.aspx "Woodworking Tool Catalog")  
---|---  
---  

[](https://www.mcafeesecure.com/RatingVerify?ref=highlandwoodworking.com) **HIGHLAND WOODWORKING** has been a dependable source for woodworking tools, books, supplies and education for over 30 years, and is family owned and operated. We invite you to visit our Highland [ **Woodworking Tool Blog**. ](http://blog.woodworkingtooltips.com/)[**Highland Affiliate Program**](https://www.highlandwoodworking.com/index.asp?PageAction=Custom&ID=131)   
Highland Woodworking Tools Affiliate Program! Give your visitors access to one of woodworking's most experienced and trusted tool retailers.
